pcdocpro.com 2010-06-03

# PC Doctor| PC Doc Pro| PC Fix| Registry Cleaner |PC Diagnostics | Registry Cleaning Utilities | PC Checkup| Clean Windows Registry

**We have a simple policy, we neither sell or share your information with anyone - never have and never will.**

**Privacy Policy**

This document sets forth the Win Doc Pro Online Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) for this Web site. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use this site. 

**PC Win Doc Pro respects your privacy**

PC Win Doc Pro values the trust you place in us by using our products and by doing business with us. If you have any concerns about our privacy policy or the manner in which we protect your privacy, please contact us immediately. 

We only collect personal information from you when necessary. For example, we collect billing and personal information necessary to sell you software from our ite. To provide effective technical support in an efficient manner, we ask for contact information allowing us to research the problem and respond. Information that you provide to us in the course of resolving technical issues is never shared with anyone outside of Win Doc Pro and is only used internally to improve our products and refine our future product plans. We give you the opportunity to sign up to receive specific e-mail notifications for which you must provide your e-mail address and reply to an opt-in confirmation request. The e-mail addresses and corresponding announcements you asked to receive are never shared with anyone outside of PC Win Doc Pro 

Entities collecting personal information 

Personal information on this Site is collected by PC Win Doc Pro 

**Collection of personal information**

As a visitor to this Site, you can engage in many activities without providing any personal information. In connection with other activities, such as subscribing to periodic mailings offered on the Site or registering software, Win Doc Pro may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you select to engage in these activities, however, PC Win Doc Pro may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including ZIP code), e-mail address, employer, job title and department, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personal information. When ordering products or services on the Site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.

When you use the Site, PC Win Doc Pro may also collect certain technical and routing information about your computer to facilitate your use of the Site and its services. For example, we may log environmental variables, such as browser type, operating system, CPU speed, and the Internet Protocol (“IP”) address of your computer. We use these environmental variables to facilitate and track your use of the Site and its services. PC Win Doc Pro also uses such environmental variables to measure traffic patterns on the Site and to refine the Site to provide the best possible user experience. Without expressly informing you in each particular circumstance, we do not match such information with any of your personal information. 

When you submit personal information to PC Win Doc Pro through this Site, you understand and agree that this information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which Win Doc Pro and its affiliates and subsidiaries maintain offices, including, without limitation, the United States. You also acknowledge that in certain countries or with respect to certain activities, the collection, transferring, storage, and processing of your information may be undertaken by trusted vendors (e.g. credit card merchant services) of PC Win Doc Pro. Such vendors are bound by contract not to use your personal information for their own purposes or provide it to any third parties. One instance where this could occur is in conjunction with development and support for localized and internationalized versions of our Site. 

**How your personal information is used**

PC Win Doc Pro collects your registration information in order to record and support your use of the software you have registered. If you register a product, for example, the information is used to register your rights, if any, to technical support or other benefits that may be made available to registered users. As another example, if you enter a contest, information is collected to qualify the entry and contact you regarding the contest or prize awards. Your personal information is also used to keep you informed about product upgrades, special offers, and other products and services of Win Doc Pro and selected third parties if you have so opted to receive such communications. 

PC Win Doc Pro may collect information about the use of the Site, such as the types of services used and how many users we receive daily. This information is collected in aggregate form, without identifying any user individually. Win Doc Pro may use this aggregate, non-identifying statistical data for statistical analysis, marketing, or similar promotional purposes. 

**Your choices with respect to personal information**

PC Win Doc Pro recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of information collected on this Site. Without your consent, Win Doc Pro will not communicate any information to you regarding products, services, and special offers available from PC Win Doc Pro, although we may find it necessary to communicate with you regarding your use of PC Win Doc Pro products that you have registered. PC Win Doc Pro will not provide your name to other companies or organizations without your consent.

PC Win Doc Pro may provide your personal information if necessary, in Win Doc Pro good faith judgment, to comply with laws or regulations of a governmental or regulatory body or in response to a valid subpoena, warrant, or order or to protect the rights of PC Win Doc Pro or others. 

**Protection of your personal information**

The personal information that you provide in connection with registering yourself as PC Win Doc Pro Affiliate is classified as Registration Information. Registration Information is protected in several ways. Access by you to your Registration Information is available through a password and unique e-mail address selected by you. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. In addition, your Registration Information resides on a secure server that only selected Win Doc Pro personnel and contractors have access to via password. Win Doc Pro encrypts your personal information and thereby strives to prevent unauthorized parties from viewing such information when it is transmitted to PC Win Doc Pro 

Personal information that you provide that does not constitute Registration Information also resides on a secure server and is only accessible to selected Win Doc Pro personnel and contractors via password. Since this information is not accessible by you, you will not be asked to select a password in order to view or modify such information.

Please note that any information you post to a public bulletin board or chat room is available to all persons accessing that location. Although we may provide links to user groups and chat rooms that discuss PC Win Doc Pro products as a convenience to our customers, we do not control the content or privacy policies of those forums. Your e-mail address will not automatically be posted on the forums unless you permit that. Your e-mail address would then be available to all persons accessing the forums. In addition, you should be aware that the Forums offers a service in which subscribers are e-mailed a copy of all messages posted to the forums on a particular topic. Consequently, if you post a message to the forums, your e-mail address will be sent to those subscribers that have indicated an interest in the topic of your message. 

**Use of cookies**

PC Win Doc Pro does not attempt to track your identity or personal information using cookies or any other mechanism. This information tracks the number of downloads or purchases made by visitors who reach PC Win Doc Pro or its subsidiaries from our affiliates’ web sites. However, no personal information is ever provided to any affiliate and the tracking information is only reported in aggregate terms.  
In addition, PC Win Doc Pro uses cookies to better understand how visitors use our web site so that we can improve usability and effectiveness. 

Updating your personal information and privacy preferences 

You have the right to access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences at any time. You may access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences (such as whether you wish to receive promotional communications from Win Doc Pro or third parties) to us at privacy (@) PC Doc Pro.com: 

Please include your name, address, and/or e-mail address when you contact us. No specific form is required to notify PC Win Doc Pro of changes to your address or privacy preferences. 

In your correspondence, please indicate with as much detail as possible the location on this Site where you provided your personal information. 

**Privacy-related inquiries and complaints**

PC Win Doc Pro takes its users’ privacy concerns seriously. If you believe that Win Doc Pro has not complied with this Online Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information or you have other related inquiries or concerns, you may write to the PC Win Doc Pro Privacy Officer at the e-mail address indicated above.

In your e-mail, please describe in as much detail as possible the nature of your inquiry or the ways in which you believe that the PC Win Doc Pro Online Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your inquiry or complaint promptly. 

Please note that if you provide PC Win Doc Pro with inconsistent privacy preferences (for example, by indicating on one occasion that third parties may contact you with marketing offers and indicating on another occasion that they may not), PC Win Doc Pro cannot guarantee that your most recent privacy preference will be honored.   
Also, please note that Win Doc Pro is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non- PC Win Doc Pro Web sites to which this Site or any other PC Win Doc Pro Web site may link. You should review the privacy policy of such sites before using the sites. 

**Changes in Privacy Policy**

All “personal information” (“personal information” is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains) that we collect and maintain will be subject to the version of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of such collection. PC Win Doc Pro reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion, and will provide notice of material changes on the home page of the Site. If as the result of such changes, you want to alter the ways in which PC Win Doc Pro is allowed to use your personal information, you can do so by following the procedure described below in the section titled “Updating your personal information and privacy preferences.” You will be deemed to have been made aware of, and will be subject to, the changes to the Privacy Policy by your continued use of the Site after such notice has been posted for thirty (30) days with the following exception: If at the time you provide personal information to PC Win Doc Pro you are given the opportunity (as you currently are) to limit how such information will be used to communicate with you, either by PC Win Doc Pro or by third parties, PC Win Doc Pro will not change your preference in this regard without your express consent. However, if PC Win Doc Pro sells assets (or the assets of a division or subsidiary) to another entity, or PC Win Doc Pro (or a division or subsidiary) is acquired by, or merged with, another entity, PC Win Doc Pro may provide to such entity customer information that is related to that part of our business that was sold to or merged with the other entity without your consent.
